smashsolution.com 2013-06-09

# Smash Solutions

Thank you for visiting the Smash Solutions, LLC ("Smash") website ("Site"). We appreciate the opportunity to interact with you on the Internet and are committed to protecting and safeguarding your privacy. The purpose of this Privacy Statement is to inform you about the types of information Smash might collect from you when you visit our Site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct that information.

**Please Read This Privacy Policy To Learn More About:**

    * What personally identifiable information of yours is collected by Smash or by third party advertisers (together, "Third Parties" or individually, "Third Party" for purposes of this Privacy Policy) and how the information is used; and
    * How you can access and change your account information.

To become a member of Smash you must create an account on our Site. The only information that will be collected by Smash is the information you provide through the registration process, and when you update your payment options. This information will include your first and last name, email address, country of origin, telephone number and possibly other non-confidential contact information. Your Internet Protocol Address ("IP Address") is recorded when you register, so that we can enforce the one account per person policy and other provisions of our Terms of Service. Other information, which does not personally identify you as an individual, may be collected via cookies and other means. Smash uses cookies to make interactions with its Site easy and meaningful. Smash may share non-personally identifiable information about you, including site URLs, site-specific statistics and similar information collected by Smash with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. This information can be utilized in the sole discretion and manner deemed appropriate by Smash.

**Information Sharing & Disclosure**

In the event that you subscribe or opt-in to a Third Party offer, Smash may provide your information to the Third Party in order to directly facilitate the relationship between you and the Third Party. Smash may also, from time to time, provide your information to Third Party advertisers who have offers that we think you would be interested in. The Third Parties receiving this information may reside in jurisdictions with less restrictive data laws than your own. Smash will not be liable to you for any disclosure of your information by any Third Party. You may, at any time, opt-out of Smash's System simply by contacting Smash's support department.

Your email address may also be used for tracking purposes when you complete various offers, so that we can determine that you completed the offers. Smash will also use your email address to send you the latest newsletters, unless you have opted out of receiving such newsletters by so indicating on the appropriate place within the Site.

**Use of Cookies on This Site**

A "cookie" is a small data file transferred to your computer's hard drive that allows a website to respond to you as an individual, gathering and remembering information about your preferences in order to tailor its operation to your needs, likes and dislikes.  
Overall, cookies are safe, as they only identify your computer to customize your web experience. Accepting a cookie does not provide access to your computer or any personally identifiable information about you, other than the information you chose to share. Other servers cannot read them, nor can they be used to deliver a virus.  
Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually adjust yours (Microsoft Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator, Google Chrome, or Mozilla Firefox) to notify you of cookie placement requests, refuse certain cookies, or decline cookies completely. Our Site does place cookies to your computer's hard drive to enhance your experience when visiting our Site. 

**Information Provided By You to Third Parties or Other Users**

You may be asked by Third Parties to give your personally identifiable information, either when you complete an offer, when you use their websites, or by some other means. Smash is not responsible for information you provide the Third Parties, and you should read their privacy policies as well before providing them with any such information. Please note, unless otherwise stated, any offer you complete on this Site will be with a Third Party.  
Any information you post on this Site or send through our message center may be available to other end users or viewers of this Site. Smash is not responsible for the information you post on this Site or for information you provide other end users, all of which you do at your own risk. 

**Links to Other Websites**

Links to third party websites may be provided solely for your information and convenience. If you use these links, you will leave our Site. This Privacy Statement does not cover the information practices of those websites linked to our Site, nor do we control their content or privacy policies.  
Smash cannot be liable for any information obtained by outside parties from your use of such links. Smash cannot guarantee absolute privacy from any hypertext links on our Site leading to other websites. We encourage you to be careful when providing information to any third parties other than Smash. We suggest that you carefully review the privacy policies of each site you visit. 

**Legal Disclaimer**

Smash may disclose any information about you to legal authorities, your Internet Service Provider, or other harmed parties without your prior permission, if we have a good-faith belief that such disclosure is warranted and/or necessary because: (1) you have violated the User Agreement Terms and Conditions, (2) you have undertaken actions which are illegal, fraudulent, or otherwise harmful to this Site, its users, or Third Parties, or such disclosure is necessary, (3) to conform to legal requirements or to comply with the legal process as required by legal jurisdictions, or (4) to protect and defend the rights of Smash in any legal, judicial or administrative proceeding.

**Managing Your Information**

You can review the personal information you have provided and make any desired changes to that information by logging in to your Smash account. By editing the information, and then by submitting the revised information your data and information will remain accessible for your use. You should update Smash on any changes that occur pertaining to your personal information. If you fail to do so your information will be inaccurate or misleading and could cause loss of your data base and could be construed as fraud under the terms of this Agreement.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

Notice of all changes that materially affect ways in which your personally identifiable information may be used or shared will be emailed to you or posted on the Smash Site. Your continued use of this Smash System after such notices of change have been sent to you or published on this Site constitutes your consent to the changes.
